# DAYNA LAUREN CABRERA

daynalaurenc@gmail.com · (707)-816-6366 · Sacramento, CA daynalaurenc.github.io/Portfolio · linkedin.com/in/daynalaurenc/

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Communication Studies and Business, and has lifelong dedication to learning. Experienced in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize, Firebase, and Node Js. Additionally, knowledgeable in Social Media marketing.

#### PROJECTS:

### Coffee Collective | Team Member

*Interactive data application for locating and rating coffee shops* 

- Worked in team of 4 to analyze coffee shops and allow users to rate based on a given criteria list.
- Used Javascript, jQuery, Chart.js, Firebase, and various APIs to collect data from coffee shops in given zip codes.

## Train Scheduler | Sole Developer

Front end train scheduling application

- Accepts user input to add new train name, start time, and frequency to schedule, based on current time.
- Used Moment.js, Firebase, Javascript, and jQuery.

### **EXPERIENCE:**

Facebook, BCForward Mountain View, CA

December 2017- November 2018

Social Media Content Review Analyst

- Met and exceeded all quotas throughout tenure; averaged more than 98% accuracy of performance and quality
- Maintained in-depth company policy and terms of service knowledge and provided feedback regarding new processes
- Worked with abuse, spam or fraud detection, trust & safety issues. Was elevated to focus on more complex reviews
- Identified trends to determine the content's level of authenticity, intent and assisted with high-priority ad hoc workloads

MAC Cosmetics San Francisco, CA November 2014– Present

Social Media Manager (December 2015— January 2017)

Product Specialist (January 2016—November 2016)

Sales Executive and Pro Makeup Artist (November 2014—Present)

- Instagram experienced +58% in followers, consistently maintained engagement rate >115%
- Top Producer in Store's Productivity Plan YTD: Personal +3% vs. Store -19%
- Successfully led in store's sell-thru turnaround—bottom ranking to #1 in numerous collection launches
- Increased clientele turnout for Industry events, gross \$100k+ revenue by implementing new team marketing strategy
- Responsible for driving sales, optimizing in-store merchandising and brand presentation, inventory focus and ensuring 'best in class' execution of brand training and client acquisition strategy

Valley Bible Church Hercules, CA March 2013 – January 2014

Administrative Assistant

- Developed new filing and organizational practices, prepared weekly portfolios needed for services
- Facilitated communication between directors and staff; procured supplies, equipment, and keys for office and events
- Performed office duties: record-keeping, filing, telephones, mail, and creating in-house postings and memorandums

Lazy Dog Restaurant

Concord, CA

October 2013 - December 2014

Trainer (June 2014— December 2014)

Service Team Member (October 2013—June 2014)

- Promoted the organization's community programs and mission of delivering outstanding client-focused service
- Managed client complaints and inspected the condition of food service environment
- Responsible for succession planning and training newly-hired staff

## **EDUCATION:**

## **UC Davis Continuing and Professional Education**

November 2018 - Present

Certificate, Web Design

San Jose State University May 2015